pakmet.com.pk 2014-06-24

# pakmet.com.pk - Privacy Policy

| www.pakmet.com.pk  
---  
PAKMET.COM.PK  
   [Home](http://www.pakmet.com.pk/) :: Bookmark    
|  |   
---  
  
We do not sell, trade, rent or make available, your personal information to others.

This Privacy Policy outlines how your personal information is treated and forms part of our Terms & Conditions Of Use. We may occasionally modify our Privacy Policy; when this happens we will notify you via our Terms of Use page. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that a web site transfers to a site visitor's hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking web site usage. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person's name or e-mail address. In order to measure the effectiveness of our on-line presence, pakmet.com.pkmay use cookies to identify repeat visitors to our site and to determine the path visitors take on our site. 

Use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you can set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.  

|   

**Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use state of the technology to track intruders and maintain our site active and protected. 

**Children's Privacy **

Some Portions of the Web site may be used by children under the age of 13. We are strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our web site.   

---  
  
|   
---|---  
|   
|    
|  **   **  
  
Copyright (C)  2014 pakmet.com.pk All Rights Reserved
